/*
 * Script for index.html
 * requires scripts.js
 */

const gameOfThrones = {
  trivia: [
    {
      question: "What is the name of Jon's direwolf?",
      answers: {
        1: 'Lady',
        2: 'Summer',
        3: 'Grey Wind',
        4: 'Ghost'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many fingertips did Stannis Baratheon chop off of Davos' hand(s)?",
      answers: {
        1: 'Four',
        2: 'Three',
        3: 'Five',
        4: 'Two'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is king of Westeros when the the series begins?',
      answers: {
        2: 'Robert Baratheon',
        1: 'Eddard Stark',
        3: 'Tywin Lannister',
        4: 'Aerys Targaryan'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question:
        'What is the name of the continent on which most of the action of "Game of Thrones" takes place?',
      answers: {
        3: 'Westeros',
        2: 'Essos',
        1: 'Iseros',
        4: 'The Shadow Lands'
      },
      correctAnswer: '3'
    },
    {
      question:
        'At the end of season 2, Joffrey Baratheon sits on the Iron Throne, but which Baratheon is actually the rightful king?',
      answers: {
        4: 'Stannis Baratheon',
        2: 'Renly Baratheon',
        3: 'Tommen Baratheon',
        1: 'Myrcella Baratheon'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
      question:
        "Why could Jon leave the Night's Watch, even though his vows were for life?",
      answers: {
        2: 'He died',
        1: 'He became King',
        3: 'He knew nothing',
        4: 'He wanted to'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the Lightning Lord?',
      answers: {
        3: 'Beric Dondarrion',
        2: 'Thoros of Myr',
        1: 'Meryn Trant',
        4: 'Randyll Tarly'
      },
      correctAnswer: '3'
    },
    {
      question:
        'In 2011, which actor who plays Tyrion Lannister, won the Golden Globe award for Best Performance by an Actor in a Supporting Role in a Series?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Peter Dinklage',
        2: 'Lena Headey',
        3: 'Nikolaj Coster-Waldau',
        4: 'Charles Dance'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who did Jon execute after his first general meeting as Lord Commander with the men of the Night's Watch?",
      answers: {
        2: 'Janos Slynt',
        1: 'Bowen Marsh',
        3: 'Alliser Thorne',
        4: 'Samwell Tarly'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which of the following types of wine does the wine merchant attempt to poison Daenerys with?',
      answers: {
        4: 'Arbor Red',
        2: 'Stormland Red',
        3: 'Vale White',
        1: 'Dornish Red'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    }
  ]
};
